ALCHEMY OF SOULS
PART 2
Uk and Bu-yeon have promised
to go their separate ways.
I heard there was
no physical intimacy between them,
so it will be easier to part ways.
It is a relief that they were not
in a deep relationship.
But I remember
the two of them
drinking together at night.
They both clearly told me that
their relationship was pure and innocent,
for nothing ever happened between them.
Just now,
I felt the energy within you.
The ice stone?
Yes.
What a powerful energy.
Do you really think I will be able
to control this and take it out?
I have always wanted to stop,
but right now, I do not.
Do not ever think that again.
Although, even if you do,
I will never grant it to you.
I am sorry.
And…
thank you.
Since we have stopped, let us think
about how to deal with this situation.
Why are you turning the light on?
Turn it back off.
If we want to be together,
we must retract the promise.
The promise was made, after all.
Lord Park was there as well
when I made that promise,
which also makes it a promise
between Songrim and Jinyowon.
That promise saved Seo Yul's life,
so it was worth it.
I will ask the leader
for his understanding
and have your mother agree
to retract the promise we made.
Have her agree to it?
Do you plan to threaten my mother?
I will convince her
just like anybody would.
"I promise to be a good man."
"Please allow me to marry your daughter."
Sounds convincing.
Try convincing me too.
No, we need to take care
of the situation first.
If we get distracted again,
it will not be easy to keep our heads.
All right.
Let us save it for later
and focus on taking care of things.
You have met my mother
without me a few times, right?
How was she then?
What have you done?
Perhaps you happen
to enjoy things like that?
Being locked up in a dark room
and getting poked by needles?
- I should not have mentioned the needles.
- Needles? What do you mean?
No, it is nothing.
I shall comply with her
even if she pokes me with needles.
Leaving you to deal with this
may not be the best idea.
I should go home as promised.
You are going to leave?
If I do not go,
it will be troublesome for Lord Park,
and my mother will only hate you more.
First, I shall go home
and put her at ease.
Then I will try talking to her.
All right, you do that.
I will also discuss it with Lord Park
and come up with a solution.
Naksu's soul will disappear
from her body soon.
Once the soul of Jin Bu-yeon,
the true owner of that body, awakens,
Naksu's soul will disappear.
Where is Young Master Seo?
He woke up and is well.
He left to meet Lord Park.
Goodbye.
I guess he went to tell him directly
what he had written in the letter.
Does that mean everyone will find out
that the woman with Young Master Jang
is Naksu?
Jang Uk, I want you
to sleep at home from now on.
- Do not sleep here.
- All right.
And tell Maidservant Kim
that I will be back soon.
I will.
I bought honey biscuits
and left them in my room.
Go and eat them.
- Honey biscuits?
- Yes.
I heard they were your favorite,
so I bought some every time I went out.
- How much did you buy?
- A lot.
You might fall down. Walk facing forward.
We will be apart for a while.
I want to look at you every chance I get.
There is not a single place
where I cannot go,
but I do not want your mother
to hate me even more,
so you should hold on.
You should secretly visit.
Climb over the wall
like Seo Yul did last time.
Look at you,
excitedly asking me to break in.
By the way,
how did you find the entrance
to where I was locked up?
That door is hard to find.
Door?
What is this?
It just opened
as if someone had left it open.
It just opened?
It is likely that I broke it
while fighting the soul shifter.
That might be why the barrier broke.
I see.
Then what did you think of me
when we first met?
I found you unusual
and suspicious for being locked up
in a room like that.
I liked you from the start.
I knew the moment I saw you.
You are my husband.
You are my master.
You once felt the same way.
The blue marks
bloomed in her eyes like flowers.
I do not care
that you did not recognize me
when we first met.
This time…
I recognized you first.
Let us go.
You should still be resting.
What was it that could not wait?
There is something I feel responsible for.
Is it something that I also need to hear?
What is it?
It is about Uk and Jin Bu-yeon.
Goodness, Yul is unbelievable.
Grandfather.
Did Young Master Seo tell you something?
He talked about Jin Bu-yeon.
He said he wishes
to take full responsibility.
The promise with Lady Jin
was made to save my life,
so I will visit her
and make sure it is retracted.
Was that all he said?
Did he say anything else
about Jin Bu-yeon?
Yun-ok.
I have told you time and again
to take your mind off anything
and everything that involves Jang Uk.
Do not even be curious about him.
He did not tell them about Naksu?
Even after he had planned
to get rid of her at Danhyanggok?
Cho-yeon left by herself?
Yes, Young Master Seo asked her
to leave without you.
Seo Yul?
How do you think
Yul is going to convince Lady Jin?
I do not know.
He just said that
my mother would wait if I told her
that Seo Yul will visit her soon
to talk about what he knows.
He is not one to speak rashly,
so his plan is one that will work.
Shall I ask him
to convince your mother about us too?
Our situation is not the same.
She utterly detests Jang Uk,
but she does not dislike you.
But…
why does she disapprove of Uk so much?
Because it agonizes her
to see the person she hates…
be so happy.
Yul is going to meet Lady Jin
and try to convince her
to retract the promise.
Yul is truly amazing.
He is helping his friend
as soon as he wakes up.
So I told him,
"Uk has already made up his mind."
"Do not get involved
and just focus on recovering."
And I stopped him.
Why would you stop him
from helping out a friend?
You told me that
you were going to give up.
- My lord.
- That is what he said.
If Young Master Seo helps,
are you willing to try
and convince Lady Jin?
I took her daughter from her
without even asking for permission,
so I understand her anger.
I will do what I can
to get rid of her hatred.
I heard the news.
Thank you for helping.
I am merely taking responsibility.
You genuinely helped us.
You may have noticed
from what I said last time,
but there was no room for me in his heart.
But now I get to stay by his side.
Is it not great?
I am not sure.
You will cause each other pain.
Why would you say that?
We are all friends, are we not?
Friends?
If you knew what I had planned
to do at Danhyanggok…
you would not smile and call me a friend.
You look unhappy.
Is it because it still hurts?
Yes.
It hurts.
Perhaps it is because I woke up
from a horrible dream.
Did you have a bad dream?
There is someone I have cherished
for a very long time…
and I dreamt of disappearing with her.
But when I woke up, it turns out…
that I will remain and she will disappear.
I feel both angry and disheartened.
But most importantly,
my heart aches for her…
and it agonizes and saddens me.
I cherish all the memories
I had in Danhyanggok.
Have we…
ever met before at Danhyanggok?
You wanted to go there
to find your true identity.
Go and find out who you really are.
Then you will realize what it was
that I had planned to do at Danhyanggok
and why you and Uk will only end up
causing each other pain.
No, I do not wish to.
I will not go
if that is what is waiting for me.
If I cannot be with Jang Uk
because of the truth…
I do not wish to find out.
You may not wish to find out…
but you will.
You asked me
to turn a blind eye
even though you were dying.
I ask the same of you.
Please turn a blind eye.
Your foolish friend will give you time.
But if you ever need me…
you can come and find me.
Young Lady Bu-yeon.
I heard the news.
I am very happy for you.
Thank you.
Young Master Jang even asked Lord Park
to help him convince your mother
to change her mind.
He did?
I knew things would turn out this way.
I am glad that it was you
who ended up with him.
Do you really think…
it will be all right for me
to stay by his side?
Of course.
Now all that is left for us to do
is to prepare for the wedding.
Young Master Jang
is meeting someone from the palace.
We should head home first.
- All right.
- Come on.
His Majesty the King
will be summoning you today.
But before that,
the Crown Prince wishes to see you.
Inside this chest is an item
that belongs to His Royal Highness.
If you happen to have the same item,
he wants you to bring it with you.
He has ordered that you open it
when no one is around you.
This is the Gold Plaque
that the King left behind for his son.
What is he playing at?
Is that the King's Star?
He is a dangerous star
who can take your place whenever he wants.
Your Royal Highness.
I just visited Jang Uk.
Good.
As for the turtle,
I could not find it anywhere.
Someone must have discarded it.
Lord Dang-gu gave orders
to hold a funeral,
but this lad insisted that
you come to see her first.
She wanted to make sure
that you were all right.
I am sure she is happy to see you well.
- What is that?
- Well…
It was something she cherished dearly.
I do not understand why.
She never even used that when it rained.
Does she not have a family member
who can hold her funeral?
No.
She said the world she knew
was filled with filth and darkness.
But she said you made the world
seem clean and bright.
Find her a place
where it is warm with lots of sunlight.
I will also attend the funeral.
Yes, Young Master.
I thought those memories came from this.
But was I wrong?
What is going on?
You will realize why you and Uk
will only end up causing each other pain.
Will I be able to find out
if I go to Danhyanggok?
Young Lady Bu-yeon.
Young Master Jang is here.
Jang Uk.
Hey.
I have to go to the palace immediately.
It will not take long.
All right.
I need to get changed.
Are you going to keep staring?
No, now is not the time
to turn the light off.
Did you get that scar
from getting stabbed by that sword?
Yes.
So that was the moment
that you were dying to know
how she felt.
Everyone says she did it
to avenge her family's death.
But I just could not know
if she truly did not
go easy on me.
It is a sad…
and terrible wound.
I do not wish to see
the memory of that moment.
Do you
still see her memories?
I just do not wish to see
someone else's memories.
They are hers, not mine.
You said seeing that tree in Danhyanggok
might help you remember who you are.
- Do you want me to go with you?
- No.
I think I was confused about that too.
We do not need to go.
You should get changed and go.
All right. Wait for me here.
Yes, I will be waiting.
What is going on?
You were feeling elated earlier,
but you seem a little down.
It is just hard to believe
that you told me to wait.
You either always told me to leave
or just never came back.
Wait here. Do not go anywhere.
All right.
I will quickly be back by your side.
I promised you…
that I will always be by your side.
You were looking for Young Master Seo.
Did you see him?
I saw him leave earlier.
No, it is fine.
I will take care of it myself.
- Here it is.
- What is that medicine for?
It is used to examine corpses
to reveal hidden scars.
A soul shifter's blue mark is like a scar,
so applying this will reveal it.
What do you plan to do with it?
She said she did not want to find out…
so I plan to show her.
I saved your life,
and you come here
to threaten me with her secret?
If it sounds like a threat, then so be it.
Do not try to keep Naksu
locked up in Jinyowon.
Are you telling me
to let her stay with Jang Uk?
If that is what she wants,
then I will help her do that.
Then that leaves me
no reason to keep Naksu alive.
You must stop thinking of it that way
if you want your daughter, Jin Bu-yeon,
to return to you safe and sound.
What?
Bu-yeon will return?
What do you mean?
Naksu's soul will disappear soon,
and Jin Bu-yeon will take over the body.
That is what Master Lee told me.
He told me Bu-yeon's soul
did not remain in that body.
Then has he been
deceiving me all this time?
Ask him yourself.
Just let her
stay where she wants
with the person she wishes to be with
for a while.
This is both a threat…
and a plea.
Why are you empty-handed?
Why did you not bring what I asked?
You also have this.
I did not bring it,
as it did not seem necessary.
I guess that means
you really do possess it.
The fact that you know I possess it
means you also know
how I came into this world.
If you do not intend
to fight me over the Gold Plaque,
go to North Fortress, Jang Uk.
I will hide behind Jin Mu like you said,
and I order you to go far away.
I, Jang Uk of the Jang family,
will abide by the royal order
and leave for North Fortress.
Thank you for honoring my command.
Do not waste any more time
and prepare to leave in a few days.
I planned to threaten Park Jin of Songrim
to put pressure on Jang Uk.
I am surprised
that you made him succumb to you
by revealing the existence
of the Gold Plaque.
I realized something
as I stood against him recently.
Jang Uk does not fight for personal gain,
but to protect those around him.
So if I challenged him
with the Gold Plaque,
I figured he would back down
to protect his loved ones.
Park Jin of Songrim
also did not do anything to me
to protect Jang Uk.
They are restrained by justice
and fail to do what is necessary.
It is a sign of weakness.
I see.
Gwanju.
Ever since a few days ago,
I cannot seem to find my turtle.
That insignificant and weak animal
does not suit you, Your Royal Highness.
Do not allow yourself
to cling to something so trivial.
Did you get rid of it
to prevent me from doing so?
Do you wish to find it again?
No.
I just think it is a shame
because I was told it had good energy.
The peacock in the garden
also holds good energy.
They are nothing but animals
that merely exist to please the eye.
Understood.
So have you agreed
to go to North Fortress?
Yes, I have decided to go.
It concerns me
that they might be sending you away
as part of a scheme.
The Crown Prince showed me his Gold Plaque
and asked if I was willing to fight.
If I decide to engage in this fight,
will you stand behind me
like you did last time?
What exactly is your target in this fight?
What is it that you wish to protect?
Are you acting in careful deliberation?
Yes, I know where I am targeting,
and I have decided to accept this fight
in order to protect what I must.
What brings you here?
Young Lady Heo wishes to meet you.
At Sejukwon?
No.
She wishes to meet
where Young Master Jang frequently visits.
We received another message
from Seoho Fortress.
Your father is very worried about you.
I will write him a letter.
Right.
We should have asked Lord Park
to take the letter
that was inside your luggage
when he visited Seoho Fortress.
You saw the letter that was in my luggage?
Yes, Young Lady Heo took it.
Where is Young Lady Heo?
Why did you ask me to meet you here?
I heard this graveyard
was built by Young Master Jang
after he started killing soul shifters.
Then there should also be a grave
for Naksu, the one who killed him.
That must be it.
You said you have
no recollection of who you are, right?
Are you not curious?
Why do you care?
Because I am curious too.
So I came to confirm something.
What is that?
I am a physician.
I would never do anything to harm anyone.
I am merely trying
to satisfy our curiosity.
- There should be a blue mark here.
- What are you doing?
- Young Master Seo.
- What do you think you are doing?
Are you all right?
I am all right.
Why did you splash that on me?
- Because you are a soul shifter--
- Enough.
If you are doing this
because of my letter, just stop.
I will explain everything.
Young Lady Bu-yeon, you should hurry
and wash off the medicine.
All right.
Did you read my letter?
I did.
If everything in that letter is true,
why are you letting her be?
She is Naksu, is she not?
The blue marks
bloomed in her eyes like flowers.
Am I…
her?
That woman…
hurt Young Master Jang very deeply.
I could not let her stay beside him
only to see him get hurt again.
So I wanted to show her who she is
and make her leave.
You do not need to let her know.
Her soul will soon disappear.
I just wanted…
to let her stay like this
for a bit longer.
You have poisoned me again,
crazy master.
It is that tree.
I have been here before.
Do you wish to go up there?
Fine.
I will take you to the top of that tree.
I knew the moment I saw you.
My crazy master.
I do not need a pupil
who does not improve.
Just die if you are not
going to do anything.
Master!
You are my master.
Master, I finally did it.
They are bird's eggs.
I also missed you.
I like you a lot.
Just one.
I will hold your hand as if it is a ring.
They were all my memories.
I was the owner of the blue jade.
I was his master,
Naksu.
You must be Jin Bu-yeon,
the owner of this body.
I see you have finally realized
who you really are.
What a shame.
If you found out
after I retrieved all of my divine powers,
you would have been able to leave
with no sadness.
Thanks to you,
my body stayed whole without running wild,
and I have regained
most of my divine powers.
You will soon have to leave this body,
for it is not your own.
Someone from Sejukwon came to see her?
Yes.
Does that mean she went to Sejukwon?
No, I offered to take her there
if that was where she was headed.
But she said she was going somewhere else.
All right, you can go.
Where did she go? She said she would wait.
It is not here.
That jade makes things
even more confusing.
Seeing that tree for myself
will help me find out who I really am.
I wonder if she actually went there.
She said she did not wish to go.
This is where they first met each other.
He proposed to her here as well.
Young Master Seo.
Is something the matter
with Young Lady Bu-yeon?
Send someone to Uk's place
and tell them that she is here.
Here you are.
I waited but you did not come.
I almost went to Danhyanggok
to look for you.
I went there.
And now…
I found out who I am.
Does that mean you regained your memory?
Yes.
Then why did you come here
instead of coming home?
I came looking for you
because you did not come.
I am sorry. I know I said I would wait.
But…
I can no longer wait for you.
I remembered something very important.
Let me make myself clear.
I do not know what kind of person
you remember yourself to be.
But I do not care.
Whatever those memories are,
- they do not matter to me.
- They matter to me.
Among the many things I remember…
there was a man I deeply cared for.
You really have a way
of surprising me
when it is least expected.
- What is your point?
- But you see…
he does not recognize me,
even if I am in front of him.
Is that so?
Then why not tell him that it is you?
I cannot.
I hurt him too gravely.
I cannot tell him it is me…
or go near him.
I feel too guilty to stay with you.
I shall go to Jinyowon.
No, wait.
You are just going to leave?
You left after you said you would wait,
and now you are leaving me
because you remember someone else?
Then am I supposed to act fine
and wish you good luck with him?
No, wait.
You said you cannot be with him
and he does not recognize you.
I really…
liked him a lot.
I liked him more than he liked me.
But I never had a chance to tell him.
Jang Uk.
Turn the light back on.
Keep your head straight.
Keep your promise and let me go.
I am sorry.
Mother.
Bu-yeon came home.
Bu-yeon?
Mother.
I have returned home
as promised.
Young Lady Bu-yeon went back to Jinyowon?
Why? She said she was going to stay.
I heard Lady Jin is not doing so well.
Did she leave because she was worried?
She wants to stay there for now.
Do not worry.
I see.
I wonder if Lady Jin
is in a severe condition.
We prepared your room for you.
Why do you wish to stay here?
This place is more familiar to me.
Besides, I do not wish to see anyone.
Do not worry about me.
I heard you will be
heading to North Fortress.
Yes.
I have discussed it with the leader,
so do not be concerned.
All right.
Did you tell Young Lady Bu-yeon?
No.
I should have told her,
but I did not get a chance to.
I knew the moment I saw you.
You are my master.
You are my husband.
Jang Uk of the Jang family
will be appointed
as the general of North Fortress.
Seo Gyeong, who possessed
the power of Hwansu,
moved to Seoho Fortress to prevent himself
from becoming a threat to the royal family
and thus achieved unity.
Jang Uk's transfer to North Fortress
will bring the same kind
of peace and stability to Daeho Fortress.
I shall protect Daeho Fortress
with the help of Cheonbugwan.
We will soon begin to prepare
for the lake's rite to pray for rain.
Jang Uk, you shall travel north
and wait for the black clouds
that will bring energy to the world.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
I hear you are married.
Will your wife be joining you?
The place is far and rough,
so she will not be coming with me.
She will be lonely here without you.
You have a long road ahead of you.
Travel safely.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Naksu's soul will disappear soon,
and Jin Bu-yeon will take over the body.
That is what Master Lee told me.
Did Naksu's soul disappear
just like he said it would?
No.
He said Bu-yeon would return
if that happened.
But that is not yet my daughter, Bu-yeon.
If he leaves for North Fortress…
I will never get to see him again.
Shall I try calling for her?
But what if she does not come?
There was a man I deeply cared for.
Who could it be?
Who could he be?
Three years have passed
since she lost her memory.
How could she still have
such strong feelings for him?
I liked him more than he liked me.
I guess it is possible
if she liked him a lot more.
But still, how could she dump me
in less than a day?
Am I more insignificant
than a brazier on a summer day?
She has a cold heart.
Turn the light back on.
You totally deceived me.
You should have
remembered everything
before I fell for you.
How am I supposed
to turn the light back on now?
I miss her like crazy
even after what she said.
I have informed Young Lady Bu-yeon
of your arrival.
Bu-yeon is aware
that you are leaving
for North Fortress tomorrow.
She wishes you a safe trip.
Tell her that I will visit
once I return.
What is going on?
Jang Uk is clinging to her.
Does that mean Bu-yeon is rejecting him?
You asked me to visit secretly
by climbing over the wall.
I took your advice to heart.
I should have destroyed this place
the last time I came.
Why are you back in this room?
Because I prefer it here.
It gives me space to think.
I thought you were leaving.
Why did you come back?
You stood there watching me leave,
so I came to say goodbye.
I heard you are traveling far away.
Goodbye.
"Goodbye"?
I usually have no problem leaving people.
But I was so dumbfounded
that I had to ask.
I get it.
He may feel more dear to you
now that you got your memory back.
But then,
why did you fall for me at first sight?
I want to ask if I look similar to him,
but that also feels inappropriate to ask.
Do not ask.
I cannot tell you anything.
Do we really look alike?
Did you fall for me
because I looked just like him?
Let us say that happened.
I liked you because you looked like him,
and you liked me
because you were confused.
Let us leave it at that.
I cannot do that!
I thought about it over and over again.
The reason I wanted you to stay
was not that I was confused or crazy.
I just…
I just like you that much.
I had buried my memories,
but you took them out
and helped me face them.
You held my hand
when I never thought I could.
You helped me sleep when I could not.
And for that…
I cannot stop anymore.
So I will be the brazier on a summer day.
This time, I will be the one waiting…
until you begin to miss me.
I will go now.
I will return sooner than expected.
Stay well.
Are you leaving now?
Yes.
The last mage of Jeongjingak is leaving.
That place is going to be
completely empty now.
This does not feel right.
I shall go to North Fortress with you.
I cannot let you go there alone.
Then what about me?
Aunt, you should stay beside my uncle.
Did you meet Young Lady Bu-yeon?
Did she not offer to go with you?
I thought she would insist on going.
She had her reasons.
Is Master Lee not here?
I wanted to see him before I left.
He stayed at Sejukwon
for a few days to treat Yul,
but he must have left again,
seeing he is no longer there.
I see.
Should we not tell Uk about Naksu?
I wanted to tell him,
but Lady Jin was against it.
Now that Naksu's soul
is going to disappear,
it makes me think that
he may be better off not knowing.
If he finds out…
it will be agonizing for both of them.
Jang Uk will agonize over something bigger
than the pain of losing a loved one.
He possesses the power of Hwansu.
If he wants, he can get rid of
Jin Bu-yeon's soul from that body
and keep Naksu's soul.
That is forbidden sorcery,
just like the alchemy of souls.
That is why it will be agonizing.
He will not be able to save her
even though he has the power to.
Jang Uk will agonize
over having to make a choice
that no ordinary human
would ever have to make.
It looks like Uk and Jin Bu-yeon
are having problems.
According to Young Lady Jin,
Uk went to see her sister,
but she refused to meet him.
Do you think Uk did not tell her
about going to North Fortress?
You are a sacred animal
with a rare kind of energy.
A turtle that possesses
the energy of the Black Tortoise.
They say the Black Tortoise
guides those who are lost
and leads them in the right direction.
I see you are heading over
to help someone find their way.
Will Cheonbugwan be starting
to make preparations for the lake's rite?
Will your secret organization
be getting involved as well?
I will soon introduce you
to the secret organization.
You promised to make me
as powerful as Jang Uk.
Tell me if you need my help
in achieving that goal.
I shall wholly support you.
- What is that?
- What happened?
- Goodness.
- They look like birds.
- What in the world are they?
- What are those things?
Are they birds?
What are they doing
in Lake Gyeongcheondaeho?
Hundreds of the same kind of earthenware
were found all over the lake.
They must have drifted to shore
after being discarded
during an attempt to smuggle them in.
They are just bird-shaped earthenware,
but they give off an ominous feeling.
Now that people have seen them
in Lake Gyeongcheondaeho,
it will cause an uproar.
No matter how bad the drought gets,
it will not dry up Lake Gyeongcheondaeho.
What are you talking about?
Lake Gyeongcheondaeho once dried up
during the burning drought
that occurred 200 years ago.
- I am telling you.
- Goodness, you are right.
- Be careful!
- What are you doing?
- Why would you touch that?
- Goodness.
- My goodness.
- What is that?
The capital is in an uproar
thanks to the earthenware
that I discarded into the lake.
Everyone is worried that
Lake Gyeongcheondaeho will dry up.
That is good to hear.
Dissent among the people
will cause the Unanimous Assembly
to actively take part
in the rite for the lake.
Songrim will strengthen their guard.
It will become more difficult to bring in
the earthenware from the volcano.
They will be used for the rite?
Bring them in with the gifts for the King
that get imported from the volcano.
Then Songrim will not
be able to do anything about it.
We need to place them
throughout the canals before the rite.
Will you allow me to do that,
Your Royal Highness?
I will inform the men of the Night Watch
who guard the city at night.
You may use them.
With their help, it will be an easy task.
Will these also be used
to dry up the world?
They just exist
to help the one that is real.
And that is
the fire bird that lives inside Jinyowon.
If we want that, we must gain control
of Jinyowon with the help
of the Unanimous assembly.
I asked you to come to discuss something
before attending
tomorrow's Unanimous Assembly.
You wished to discuss something with me?
The priestess who will be
dancing for the rite
will be picked from another family.
What?
The dance for the lake's rite
has been the job
of a Jinyowon priestess for centuries.
Why would you pick a priestess
from another family?
There is no one in Jinyowon
who possesses the divine powers
to dance for the lake's rite.
I am capable, and so are my two daughters.
Ho-gyeong.
I am merely here to give you notice.
The mages of the Unanimous Assembly
have already made up their minds.
If you continue
to feed your ego like this,
you will only end up
embarrassing yourself.
You will be the one embarrassing yourself.
Jinyowon will not provide you
with any of its artifacts
to help you hold the lake's rite.
The royal family and Unanimous Assembly
stand on my side.
You will eventually have to give in.
Did you forget that Jinyowon owns a plaque
that gives us the power
to reject the King's orders?
Bu-yeon.
Is it not suffocating here?
I am going to meet Young Master Park.
You should also get some air.
Mother is not home right now.
I am fine.
My lady.
Lady Jin asked you
to urgently come to Cheonbugwan
with the Jinyowon Plaque.
Now?
Right this moment?
She had a dispute with Jin Mu,
the Gwanju of Cheonbugwan.
You should hurry over.
- Did you say Jin Mu of Cheonbugwan?
- Yes.
Then I will go instead.
You?
I am the eldest daughter.
The Jinyowon Plaque
is a very valuable item.
If I let you take it,
I could get scolded by Mother.
Are you going to be the heir of Jinyowon?
Then you will have to marry a man
who is willing to move in.
But you cannot marry Park Dang-gu
since he is the leader of Songrim.
I will go.
All right.
You can go instead, Bu-yeon.
Among the many things I remember,
Jin Mu is one of them.
The man who trained me to be an assassin,
used me, and killed me.
And now,
I will be meeting him.
The Jinyowon Plaque will arrive soon.
Your trusted plaque of Jinyowon
will also be taken away tomorrow
by the Unanimous Assembly.
For what good reason?
You put Jinyowon in grave danger
for personal reasons.
He says it is not something
that can be overlooked.
- Who in the world--
- I said that.
You made a personal promise with Songrim
and allowed them
to disturb the fire bird's barrier
inside Jinyowon.
I was there when it happened.
But you helped in that matter,
Your Royal Highness.
The truth is that you allowed them
to meddle with the barrier.
And a spell was used inside Jinyowon,
which could have woken
the relics and artifacts there.
That is why
I stood outside Jinyowon
to prevent that from happening.
I used my divine powers
to keep everything safe.
Ho-gyeong.
Your hair has started to turn gray.
Your divine powers have weakened
and are no longer like they were before.
That is the main reason
why we are withdrawing the plaque.
What are you doing here?
Did you get kicked out?
Now that the plaque is on its way,
you can just leave it here.
As your brother, I do not wish
to see you embarrass yourself
in front of the Unanimous Assembly
by trying to prove your strength
when we all know that you have weakened.
People from Jinyowon are here.
Bu-yeon, why are you…
Hello, I am Jin Bu-yeon,
the eldest daughter of the Jin family.
I see you came
instead of your sister, Jin Cho-yeon.
Mother, here is the plaque you asked for.
Thank you for bringing it here.
Now leave the plaque and go home.
Why should we leave it here?
It is the Jin family's most valuable item.
Your mother has acknowledged the fact
that no one in your family
is capable of protecting the plaque.
Ho-gyeong.
Put down the plaque.
My duty as the leader of Jinyowon
is to protect this with my life.
What can I do
to make you change your mind?
I do not recall standing like that
the last time I went to you
to beg for my life.
What if I prove it to you?
I, the heir of Jinyowon,
will prove that I am capable
of keeping it safe.
I heard you lost your memory
due to a severe illness.
They say you once possessed divine powers
as great as Jin Seol-ran's,
but you lost them with your memories.
Both my divine powers and memories
have started to come back.
Is that so?
Then allow me to test your divine powers.
Fine.
What do you wish for me to show you?
This prison in Cheonbugwan
holds those who once performed sorcery.
Behind that door is a prison named Gwido.
The door that leads to Gwido
was created by Jin Seol-ran,
the first leader of Jinyowon,
so you must know it well, Ho-gyeong.
Once you enter,
you can never escape this prison,
even as a ghost.
What do you think you are doing?
Is that where you are
going to send Bu-yeon?
I am not going to lock her up.
A long time ago, Bu-yeon managed to find
the ice stone that was sealed
inside Lake Gyeongcheondaeho.
I will throw the plaque inside Gwido.
If she successfully
brings it back in a day…
then I shall acknowledge
your divine powers
and cancel tomorrow's Unanimous Assembly.
I will go in.
No.
The wraiths of those
who performed sorcery live inside Gwido.
Those wraiths could kill you.
Then do you plan to surrender Jinyowon?
Have faith in
your daughter's divine powers.
I promise
that I will bring it back.
Making her go inside Gwido
is too dangerous.
A mage from the Choi family
also died there 200 years ago.
What will you do if a Jinyowon priestess
also dies in there?
That kind of thought
is also a sign of weakness.
Find the plaque before the sun goes down.
What is that?
I found it on my way here.
The animal possesses good energy,
so I would like to take it with me.
Go ahead.
I thought it was a prison.
I had no idea it would be this vast.
How am I going to find
that small plaque here?
What if it fell into the sea?
Are you all right?
Jang Uk?
What are you doing here alone?
How are you here?
More importantly…
what is that?
What?
Those marks in your eyes.
You…
Who are you?
ALCHEMY OF SOULS
PART 2
Keep it in mind.
Only I am allowed to come this close.
Did you perhaps hear the sound of bells
during that time?
We will live in a world
where the strong gain greater power
and continue to rule forever!
All of them will have to be
eradicated for this to end.
I will likely meet my end
in this place as well.
The world they wish to see
will never come.
Is this not the kind of world you wanted?
Take a close look at what it is like
for someone with strength
to gain and wield even greater power.
Subtitle translation by: Joy Lee